<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="verse_text_1">In the beginning God created the heaven and the earth.</string>
    <string name="verse_text_2">"For God so loved the world, that he gave his only begotten Son, that whosoever believeth in him should not perish, but have everlasting life."As</string>
    <string name="verse_text_3">"Trust in the Lord with all thine heart; and lean not unto thine own understanding. In all thy ways acknowledge him, and he shall direct thy paths."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_4">"And we know that all things work together for good to them that love God, to them who are the called according to his purpose."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_5">"For the wages of sin is death; but the gift of God is eternal life through Jesus Christ our Lord."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_6">"But seek ye first the kingdom of God, and his righteousness; and all these things shall be added unto you."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_7">"Let not your heart be troubled: ye believe in God, believe also in me.</string>
    <string name="verse_text_8">"And he said unto them, Go ye into all the world, and preach the gospel to every creature."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_9">"For by grace are ye saved through faith; and that not of yourselves: it is the gift of God:"</string>
    <string name="verse_text_10">"Let your light so shine before men, that they may see your good works, and glorify your Father which is in heaven."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_11">"And the peace of God, which passeth all understanding, shall keep your hearts and minds through Christ Jesus."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_12">"Thy word is a lamp unto my feet, and a light unto my path."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_13">"For by him were all things created, that are in heaven, and that are in earth, visible and invisible, whether they be thrones, or dominions, or principalities, or powers: all things were created by him, and for him:"</string>
    <string name="verse_text_14">"He that findeth his life shall lose it: and he that loseth his life for my sake shall find it."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_15">"And the Lord, he it is that doth go before thee; he will be with thee, he will not fail thee, neither forsake thee: fear not, neither be dismayed."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_16">"For I know the thoughts that I think toward you, saith the Lord, thoughts of peace, and not of evil, to give you an expected end."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_17">"For the word of God is quick, and powerful, and sharper than any two-edged sword, piercing even to the dividing asunder of soul and spirit, and of the joints and marrow, and is a discerner of the thoughts and intents of the heart."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_18">"Blessed are the poor in spirit: for theirs is the kingdom of heaven."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_19">"For as the body without the spirit is dead, so faith without works is dead also."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_20">"And the Lord said, My spirit shall not always strive with man, for that he also is flesh: yet his days shall be an hundred and twenty years."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_21">"For whosoever shall call upon the name of the Lord shall be saved."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_22">"But love ye your enemies, and do good, and lend, hoping for nothing again; and your reward shall be great, and ye shall be the children of the Highest: for he is kind unto the unthankful and to the evil."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_23">"Therefore if thou bring thy gift to the altar, and there rememberest that thy brother hath ought against thee; Leave there thy gift before the altar, and go thy way; first be reconciled to thy brother, and then come and offer thy gift."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_24">"I will lift up mine eyes unto the hills, from whence cometh my help. My help cometh from the Lord, which made heaven and earth."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_25">"He that overcometh shall inherit all things; and I will be his God, and he shall be my son."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_26">"For all have sinned, and come short of the glory of God;"</string>
    <string name="verse_text_27">"For the eyes of the Lord are over the righteous, and his ears are open unto their prayers: but the face of the Lord is against them that do evil."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_28">"But go ye and learn what that meaneth, I will have mercy, and not sacrifice: for I am not come to call the righteous, but sinners to repentance."</string>
    <string name="verse_text_29">"For the wrath of God is revealed from heaven against all ungodliness and unrighteousness of men, who hold the truth in unrighteousness;" </string>
    <string name="verse_text_30">"Thou wilt keep him in perfect peace, whose mind is stayed on thee: because he trusteth in thee."</string>
</resources>